// Instructions for StockApp\App.xaml.cs updates:
1. Add the System.Net.Http namespace import at the top
2. After the IAuthenticationService registration, add:
   // Register the AuthenticationDelegatingHandler
   services.AddTransient<AuthenticationDelegatingHandler>();
3. For each HTTP client registration except IAuthenticationService, update it like this:
   services.AddHttpClient<IServiceInterface, ServiceImplementation>(client =>
   {
       client.BaseAddress = new Uri(apiBaseUrl);
   }).AddHttpMessageHandler<AuthenticationDelegatingHandler>();
4. Additionally, you may need to update the proxy service classes to not use manual authorization header addition, as you've already done for several of them.
5. The AuthenticationService's HttpClient should not use the DelegatingHandler to avoid circular dependencies.
